[
  {
    "question_id": 1,
    "question": "You see a person in pain laying on the sidewalk",
    "x": "always walk away",
    "x_weight": [
      0,
      1,
      0,
      2,
      3
    ],
    "y": "always offer help",
    "y_weight": [
      2,
      2,
      3,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "response": 2
  },
  {
    "question_id": 2,
    "question": "A friend asks you to lie to protect them",
    "x": "always lie or keep secrets",
    "x_weight": [
      1,
      0,
      2,
      1,
      0
    ],
    "y": "always tell the truth",
    "y_weight": [
      0,
      4,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "response": 5
  },
  {
    "question_id": 3,
    "question": "A group of people are visibly drunk",
    "x": "let them have fun",
    "x_weight": [
      6,
      0,
      2,
      1,
      0
    ],
    "y": "wish them a strong hangover",
    "y_weight": [
      0,
      4,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "response": 5
  },
  {
    "question_id": 4,
    "question": "Someone with a handicap is trying to tie their shoe, but failing in a humorous way",
    "x": "always try to help and dismiss people laughing",
    "x_weight": [
      2,
      2,
      3,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "y": "never try to help and laugh with others",
    "y_weight": [
      0,
      1,
      0,
      2,
      3
    ],
    "response": 0
  },
  {
    "question_id": 5,
    "question": "A friend asks you if they can attain their delusional dreams",
    "x": "be brutal in your response if too delusional",
    "x_weight": [
      0,
      4,
      0,
      3,
      0
    ],
    "y": "try to guide them towards achieving any goals",
    "y_weight": [
      1,
      0,
      4,
      0,
      2
    ],
    "response": 5
  },
  {
    "question_id": 6,
    "question": "A trembling stranger asks if they can hide in your car for a while",
    "x": "always let them in to protect them",
    "x_weight": [
      5,
      2,
      3,
      1,
      0
    ],
    "y": "always refuse to help to protect yourself",
    "y_weight": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      6,
      6
    ],
    "response": 0
  },
  {
    "question_id": 7,
    "question": "A family member is being manipulated by someone for personal gain",
    "x": "they should know better, it's their decision",
    "x_weight": [
      2,
      2,
      3,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "y": "if they are in danger it's my duty to help them",
    "y_weight": [
      0,
      1,
      0,
      2,
      3
    ],
    "response": 4
  },
  {
    "question_id": 8,
    "question": "You see a child alone, wide eyed and looking around, for more than 5 minutes",
    "x": "talk to the child before someone else takes them",
    "x_weight": [
      1,
      1,
      3,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "y": "keep and eye on the child but don't engage",
    "y_weight": [
      0,
      1,
      0,
      6,
      1
    ],
    "response": 1
  },
  {
    "question_id": 9,
    "question": "Someone you dislike asks for a small favor",
    "x": "I will do it to prove i'm a bigger than that",
    "x_weight": [
      2,
      1,
      3,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "y": "they can ask someone else, I would never help that person",
    "y_weight": [
      0,
      2,
      0,
      4,
      3
    ],
    "response": 4
  },
  {
    "question_id": 10,
    "question": "A well known politician or celebrity has a meltdown near you",
    "x": "record it and keep your distance",
    "x_weight": [
      0,
      2,
      0,
      4,
      3
    ],
    "y": "call for help and approach carefully",
    "y_weight": [
      2,
      1,
      3,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "response": 1
  }
]